const quizDataFromFile = [
  {
    "question": "an sein",
    "correct": "to be (switched) on",
    "choices": [
      "young",
      "from",
      "cheap",
      "to be (switched) on"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "arbeitslos",
    "correct": "unemployed",
    "choices": [
      "without",
      "interested in culture",
      "my",
      "unemployed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "auch",
    "correct": "also",
    "choices": [
      "also",
      "for",
      "him/her",
      "little / not very much"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "auf",
    "correct": "on/until/in",
    "choices": [
      "she",
      "what",
      "two hundred",
      "on/until/in"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "auf sein",
    "correct": "to be open",
    "choices": [
      "to where",
      "to be open",
      "to take (duration)",
      "one square metre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aus",
    "correct": "from",
    "choices": [
      "quiet",
      "from",
      "last",
      "who"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ausländisch",
    "correct": "foreign",
    "choices": [
      "to be on",
      "time: 24:00",
      "foreign",
      "thirty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "aus sein",
    "correct": "to be (switched) off/to be out",
    "choices": [
      "valid",
      "time: 07:15",
      "one kilo(gram)",
      "to be (switched) off/to be out"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "automatisch",
    "correct": "automatic",
    "choices": [
      "time: 07:15",
      "automatic",
      "still",
      "here / where we are"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bar",
    "correct": "cash",
    "choices": [
      "seventeen",
      "eight",
      "twenty",
      "cash"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bei",
    "correct": "next to/at/for",
    "choices": [
      "you (polite)",
      "sixty",
      "next to/at/for",
      "yourself"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bei uns",
    "correct": "here / where we are",
    "choices": [
      "ten",
      "for",
      "here / where we are",
      "when"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "beide",
    "correct": "both",
    "choices": [
      "third",
      "someone",
      "both",
      "expensive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zum Beispiel/z. B.",
    "correct": "for example",
    "choices": [
      "as",
      "no",
      "for example",
      "nothing"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bekannt",
    "correct": "well known",
    "choices": [
      "long",
      "here",
      "one metre fifteen",
      "well known"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der/die Bekannte, -n",
    "correct": "acquaintance",
    "choices": [
      "broken",
      "nineteen",
      "acquaintance",
      "quick / fast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "besetzt",
    "correct": "busy/taken",
    "choices": [
      "quiet",
      "busy/taken",
      "who",
      "one square metre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "best-",
    "correct": "best",
    "choices": [
      "best",
      "tired",
      "four",
      "acquaintance"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "billig",
    "correct": "cheap",
    "choices": [
      "single",
      "from there",
      "cheap",
      "please"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bis",
    "correct": "to (as far as)/until",
    "choices": [
      "to (as far as)/until",
      "to prefer",
      "when",
      "after / past (time)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bitte",
    "correct": "please",
    "choices": [
      "long",
      "above",
      "time: 00:03",
      "please"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bitter",
    "correct": "bitter",
    "choices": [
      "bitter",
      "your [pl.]",
      "bad",
      "ago"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "breit",
    "correct": "wide",
    "choices": [
      "bitter",
      "wide",
      "married",
      "fifty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "circa/ca.",
    "correct": "approximately",
    "choices": [
      "your",
      "approximately",
      "thirteen",
      "once"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "da",
    "correct": "there/here",
    "choices": [
      "there/here",
      "until",
      "high",
      "thirteen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "danke",
    "correct": "thank you",
    "choices": [
      "to be open",
      "one quarter; quarter",
      "there (to that place, in that direction)",
      "thank you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dauern",
    "correct": "to take (duration)",
    "choices": [
      "another",
      "favourite",
      "one pound",
      "to take (duration)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dein-",
    "correct": "your",
    "choices": [
      "twenty",
      "fifty",
      "one / impersonal ‘you’",
      "your"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dein-",
    "correct": "yourself",
    "choices": [
      "time: 13:17",
      "until",
      "loud",
      "yourself"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "denn",
    "correct": "because",
    "choices": [
      "your",
      "third",
      "fourth",
      "because"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das",
    "correct": "that/the",
    "choices": [
      "normal",
      "high",
      "same",
      "that/the"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der",
    "correct": "the",
    "choices": [
      "the",
      "degrees",
      "you",
      "until"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die",
    "correct": "the",
    "choices": [
      "the",
      "to be gone",
      "…",
      "to be (switched) on"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dich",
    "correct": "you",
    "choices": [
      "also",
      "third",
      "for",
      "you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dies-",
    "correct": "this",
    "choices": [
      "in",
      "ago",
      "once",
      "this"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dir",
    "correct": "you",
    "choices": [
      "two hundred kilometres",
      "you",
      "of (possessive “s\")",
      "to take (duration)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dort",
    "correct": "there",
    "choices": [
      "there",
      "bad",
      "for",
      "yourself"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dorthin",
    "correct": "there (to that place, in that direction)",
    "choices": [
      "over",
      "for",
      "there (to that place, in that direction)",
      "slow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dorther",
    "correct": "from there",
    "choices": [
      "nine",
      "from there",
      "free",
      "with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "durch",
    "correct": "through",
    "choices": [
      "funny",
      "through",
      "ten",
      "that"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "eilig",
    "correct": "hurry",
    "choices": [
      "five",
      "lovely",
      "same",
      "hurry"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein-",
    "correct": "one / a/someone",
    "choices": [
      "one / a/someone",
      "by",
      "cheap",
      "to where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "einfach",
    "correct": "simple/a single (ticket)",
    "choices": [
      "as",
      "simple/a single (ticket)",
      "at the weekend",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "noch einmal",
    "correct": "again",
    "choices": [
      "as",
      "time: 07:15",
      "again",
      "here / where we are"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "einmal",
    "correct": "once",
    "choices": [
      "to be out",
      "from where",
      "interested in culture",
      "once"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "er",
    "correct": "he",
    "choices": [
      "to prefer",
      "two hundred",
      "to take (duration)",
      "he"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "es",
    "correct": "it",
    "choices": [
      "high",
      "it",
      "very",
      "one percent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "euer",
    "correct": "your [pl.]",
    "choices": [
      "your [pl.]",
      "very",
      "my",
      "still"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "feiern",
    "correct": "to celebrate",
    "choices": [
      "at",
      "later",
      "finished / ready / done",
      "to celebrate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fertig",
    "correct": "finished / ready / done",
    "choices": [
      "until",
      "far",
      "finished / ready / done",
      "unemployed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "frei",
    "correct": "free",
    "choices": [
      "tired",
      "lovely",
      "free",
      "very"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fremd",
    "correct": "foreign",
    "choices": [
      "time: 07:15",
      "a single (ticket)",
      "foreign",
      "yourself"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "früher",
    "correct": "earlier / in the past",
    "choices": [
      "earlier / in the past",
      "ten",
      "because",
      "last"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "für",
    "correct": "for",
    "choices": [
      "like this",
      "for",
      "because",
      "return"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "es gibt",
    "correct": "there is/are",
    "choices": [
      "over",
      "far",
      "to take (duration)",
      "there is/are"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gerade",
    "correct": "now",
    "choices": [
      "now",
      "here",
      "to prefer",
      "late"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "geradeaus",
    "correct": "straight on",
    "choices": [
      "twenty",
      "grey",
      "straight on",
      "unemployed"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gleich",
    "correct": "same",
    "choices": [
      "three",
      "same",
      "more",
      "wonderful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gleich",
    "correct": "same/now",
    "choices": [
      "without",
      "same/now",
      "once",
      "long"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Grad (Celsius)",
    "correct": "degrees",
    "choices": [
      "time: 00:03",
      "degrees",
      "foreign",
      "thank you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gültig",
    "correct": "valid",
    "choices": [
      "valid",
      "time: 07:15",
      "to (somewhere)",
      "degrees"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "günstig",
    "correct": "cheap",
    "choices": [
      "over",
      "same",
      "cheap",
      "I"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hallo",
    "correct": "hello",
    "choices": [
      "next",
      "hello",
      "here",
      "someone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hier",
    "correct": "here",
    "choices": [
      "simple",
      "first",
      "left",
      "here"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hoch",
    "correct": "high",
    "choices": [
      "to do",
      "high",
      "two thousand and fourteen",
      "important"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ich",
    "correct": "I",
    "choices": [
      "please",
      "from",
      "acquaintance",
      "I"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ihm/ihr",
    "correct": "him/her",
    "choices": [
      "further",
      "tired",
      "him/her",
      "thirteen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ihn",
    "correct": "him",
    "choices": [
      "without",
      "from",
      "him",
      "very"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "in",
    "correct": "in/to",
    "choices": [
      "bitter",
      "in/to",
      "straight on",
      "on"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "international",
    "correct": "international",
    "choices": [
      "nineteen ninety nine",
      "late",
      "across",
      "international"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ja",
    "correct": "yes",
    "choices": [
      "another",
      "above",
      "across",
      "yes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jed-",
    "correct": "every",
    "choices": [
      "two",
      "and",
      "every",
      "same"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "jung",
    "correct": "young",
    "choices": [
      "until",
      "young",
      "here",
      "there (to that place, in that direction)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kaputt",
    "correct": "broken",
    "choices": [
      "the",
      "broken",
      "short",
      "it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(Kredit)-Karte, -n",
    "correct": "(credit) card",
    "choices": [
      "twenty",
      "(credit) card",
      "from there",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kein",
    "correct": "no/none",
    "choices": [
      "quarter to/past two (two o’clock)",
      "no/none",
      "taken",
      "to look after"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "klar",
    "correct": "of course / naturally",
    "choices": [
      "how",
      "of course / naturally",
      "automatic",
      "to where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "krank",
    "correct": "ill",
    "choices": [
      "ill",
      "another",
      "there (to that place, in that direction)",
      "which"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kulturell interessiert",
    "correct": "interested in culture",
    "choices": [
      "now",
      "sick",
      "eight",
      "interested in culture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kulturell",
    "correct": "cultural",
    "choices": [
      "cultural",
      "once",
      "one",
      "now"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sich kümmern",
    "correct": "to look after",
    "choices": [
      "grey",
      "to prefer",
      "…",
      "to look after"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "kurz",
    "correct": "short",
    "choices": [
      "here",
      "short",
      "single",
      "late"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lang",
    "correct": "long",
    "choices": [
      "long",
      "until",
      "grey",
      "return"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lange",
    "correct": "long",
    "choices": [
      "long",
      "so",
      "through",
      "little / not very much"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "langsam",
    "correct": "slow",
    "choices": [
      "until",
      "to be open",
      "loud",
      "slow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "laut",
    "correct": "loud",
    "choices": [
      "where",
      "young",
      "more",
      "loud"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ledig",
    "correct": "single",
    "choices": [
      "ill",
      "single",
      "for",
      "one half; half"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "leicht",
    "correct": "light (weight)/easy",
    "choices": [
      "you (polite)",
      "light (weight)/easy",
      "later",
      "time: 13:17"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "leider",
    "correct": "unfortunately",
    "choices": [
      "young",
      "unfortunately",
      "what",
      "one percent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "leise",
    "correct": "quiet",
    "choices": [
      "quiet",
      "sixteen",
      "a lot",
      "return"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "letzt-",
    "correct": "last",
    "choices": [
      "seventeen",
      "why",
      "last",
      "open"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lieb-",
    "correct": "dear",
    "choices": [
      "you (polite)",
      "favourite",
      "dear",
      "until"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lieber",
    "correct": "to prefer",
    "choices": [
      "in",
      "finished / ready / done",
      "to prefer",
      "four"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Lieblings-",
    "correct": "favourite",
    "choices": [
      "you (polite)",
      "favourite",
      "two thousand and fourteen",
      "when"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "links",
    "correct": "left",
    "choices": [
      "seventeen",
      "left",
      "as",
      "on"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lustig",
    "correct": "funny",
    "choices": [
      "in",
      "funny",
      "fifteen",
      "he"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "man",
    "correct": "one / impersonal ‘you’",
    "choices": [
      "your",
      "there (to that place, in that direction)",
      "four degrees above zero/plus four degrees",
      "one / impersonal ‘you’"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mehr",
    "correct": "more",
    "choices": [
      "you (polite)",
      "later",
      "more",
      "with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mein",
    "correct": "my",
    "choices": [
      "you",
      "next to",
      "my",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "meist-",
    "correct": "most",
    "choices": [
      "…",
      "one quarter; quarter",
      "most",
      "to be (switched) off"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "mit",
    "correct": "with",
    "choices": [
      "ninety",
      "two thousand and fourteen",
      "one centimetre",
      "with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "müde",
    "correct": "tired",
    "choices": [
      "six",
      "tired",
      "very",
      "for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nach",
    "correct": "to (somewhere)",
    "choices": [
      "to (somewhere)",
      "approximately",
      "last",
      "one o'clock"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nach",
    "correct": "after / past (time)",
    "choices": [
      "further",
      "right",
      "to be open",
      "after / past (time)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nächst-",
    "correct": "next",
    "choices": [
      "next",
      "in",
      "when",
      "how"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nein",
    "correct": "no",
    "choices": [
      "nine",
      "cultural",
      "no",
      "important"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nichts",
    "correct": "nothing",
    "choices": [
      "bitter",
      "yellow",
      "nothing",
      "both"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "noch",
    "correct": "still/another",
    "choices": [
      "without",
      "across",
      "still/another",
      "to look after"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "normal",
    "correct": "normal",
    "choices": [
      "tired",
      "half past two",
      "normal",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nur",
    "correct": "only",
    "choices": [
      "now",
      "to (somewhere)",
      "only",
      "heavy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "oder",
    "correct": "or",
    "choices": [
      "or",
      "our",
      "from",
      "international"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "geöffnet",
    "correct": "open",
    "choices": [
      "one o'clock",
      "left",
      "same",
      "open"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ohne",
    "correct": "without",
    "choices": [
      "without",
      "ninety",
      "bitter",
      "for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "rechts",
    "correct": "right",
    "choices": [
      "right",
      "every",
      "four degrees above zero/plus four degrees",
      "bad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ruhig",
    "correct": "quiet",
    "choices": [
      "quiet",
      "simple",
      "it",
      "when"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schlecht",
    "correct": "sick/bad",
    "choices": [
      "until",
      "sick/bad",
      "grey",
      "very"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schnell",
    "correct": "quick / fast",
    "choices": [
      "as",
      "quiet",
      "how",
      "quick / fast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schön",
    "correct": "lovely/beautiful",
    "choices": [
      "light (weight)",
      "lovely/beautiful",
      "next to",
      "when"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "schwer",
    "correct": "heavy/difficult",
    "choices": [
      "above",
      "broken",
      "fourth",
      "heavy/difficult"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sehr",
    "correct": "very",
    "choices": [
      "(one) hundred",
      "very",
      "one centimetre",
      "foreign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sehr",
    "correct": "very",
    "choices": [
      "for",
      "very",
      "taken",
      "three"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "an sein",
    "correct": "to be on",
    "choices": [
      "to be on",
      "half past two",
      "you",
      "expensive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "auf sein",
    "correct": "to be open",
    "choices": [
      "first",
      "to be open",
      "until",
      "to where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "weg sein",
    "correct": "to be gone",
    "choices": [
      "half past two",
      "what",
      "to be gone",
      "fourth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zu sein",
    "correct": "to be closed",
    "choices": [
      "to be closed",
      "for",
      "of (possessive “s\")",
      "time: 24:00"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "seit",
    "correct": "for (an amount of time)",
    "choices": [
      "where",
      "half past two",
      "to prefer",
      "for (an amount of time)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "selbstständig",
    "correct": "independent",
    "choices": [
      "in",
      "same",
      "independent",
      "to be (switched) on"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sich",
    "correct": "yourself",
    "choices": [
      "high",
      "brown",
      "there (to that place, in that direction)",
      "yourself"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sie",
    "correct": "she",
    "choices": [
      "she",
      "two",
      "to hurt",
      "after / past (time)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sie",
    "correct": "you (polite)",
    "choices": [
      "you (polite)",
      "to do",
      "high",
      "simple"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "so",
    "correct": "like this/so/as",
    "choices": [
      "best",
      "like this/so/as",
      "eighteen",
      "with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "spät",
    "correct": "late",
    "choices": [
      "second",
      "interested in culture",
      "late",
      "only"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "später",
    "correct": "later",
    "choices": [
      "seventy",
      "in",
      "later",
      "when"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "teuer",
    "correct": "expensive",
    "choices": [
      "one quarter; quarter",
      "cash",
      "heavy",
      "expensive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tot",
    "correct": "dead",
    "choices": [
      "far",
      "only",
      "both",
      "dead"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tschüss",
    "correct": "...",
    "choices": [
      "there is/are",
      "again",
      "he",
      "..."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tun",
    "correct": "to do",
    "choices": [
      "to do",
      "two",
      "one metre fifteen",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "über",
    "correct": "across/above/over",
    "choices": [
      "until",
      "please",
      "across/above/over",
      "one percent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "um",
    "correct": "at/around",
    "choices": [
      "our",
      "at/around",
      "it",
      "hello"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "und",
    "correct": "and",
    "choices": [
      "the",
      "and",
      "across",
      "last"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "unser-",
    "correct": "our",
    "choices": [
      "our",
      "how",
      "automatic",
      "open"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "unter",
    "correct": "below",
    "choices": [
      "there",
      "over",
      "someone",
      "below"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "verheiratet",
    "correct": "married",
    "choices": [
      "right",
      "married",
      "finished / ready / done",
      "to where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "viel",
    "correct": "a lot",
    "choices": [
      "married",
      "a lot",
      "for",
      "thirty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "von",
    "correct": "of (possessive “s\")",
    "choices": [
      "quiet",
      "left",
      "of (possessive “s\")",
      "easy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "von",
    "correct": "from",
    "choices": [
      "for example",
      "the",
      "high",
      "from"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vor",
    "correct": "ago/in front of",
    "choices": [
      "quiet",
      "for",
      "still",
      "ago/in front of"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wandern",
    "correct": "to hike",
    "choices": [
      "to hike",
      "loud",
      "him/her",
      "who"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wann",
    "correct": "when",
    "choices": [
      "time: 13:17",
      "(credit) card",
      "far",
      "when"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "warum",
    "correct": "why",
    "choices": [
      "every",
      "why",
      "two hundred kilometres",
      "expensive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "was",
    "correct": "what",
    "choices": [
      "what",
      "five",
      "from where",
      "dead"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "was für ein",
    "correct": "what kind of",
    "choices": [
      "without",
      "one",
      "what kind of",
      "with"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "weh tun",
    "correct": "to hurt",
    "choices": [
      "bitter",
      "first",
      "to hurt",
      "slow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "weit",
    "correct": "far",
    "choices": [
      "one pound",
      "far",
      "last",
      "one / a"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "weiter",
    "correct": "further",
    "choices": [
      "further",
      "by",
      "him/her",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "welch-",
    "correct": "which",
    "choices": [
      "quiet",
      "wide",
      "there",
      "which"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wenig",
    "correct": "little / not very much",
    "choices": [
      "quarter to/past two (two o’clock)",
      "broken",
      "still",
      "little / not very much"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wer",
    "correct": "who",
    "choices": [
      "brown",
      "for",
      "who",
      "to be (switched) off"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wichtig",
    "correct": "important",
    "choices": [
      "fourteen",
      "no",
      "to prefer",
      "important"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wie",
    "correct": "what/like/as/how",
    "choices": [
      "how",
      "best",
      "what/like/as/how",
      "foreign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wie viel",
    "correct": "how much",
    "choices": [
      "how much",
      "to hike",
      "for",
      "one pound"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wir",
    "correct": "we",
    "choices": [
      "funny",
      "for",
      "we",
      "cash"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wo",
    "correct": "where",
    "choices": [
      "where",
      "time: 07:15",
      "nineteen",
      "one / impersonal ‘you’"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "woher",
    "correct": "from where",
    "choices": [
      "so",
      "left",
      "from where",
      "for"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wohin",
    "correct": "to where",
    "choices": [
      "to be (switched) off",
      "one / a",
      "important",
      "to where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "wunderbar",
    "correct": "wonderful",
    "choices": [
      "sick",
      "one hundred and one",
      "wonderful",
      "ago"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zurzeit",
    "correct": "at the moment",
    "choices": [
      "at the moment",
      "fourty",
      "here / where we are",
      "..."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zu",
    "correct": "to/by/at",
    "choices": [
      "to/by/at",
      "best",
      "as",
      "on"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zurück",
    "correct": "return/back",
    "choices": [
      "there",
      "what",
      "here",
      "return/back"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "eins",
    "correct": "one",
    "choices": [
      "twenty",
      "one",
      "two hundred",
      "two"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zwei",
    "correct": "two",
    "choices": [
      "two",
      "to hurt",
      "who",
      "bad"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "drei",
    "correct": "three",
    "choices": [
      "simple",
      "he",
      "there (to that place, in that direction)",
      "three"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vier",
    "correct": "four",
    "choices": [
      "yellow",
      "and",
      "four",
      "this"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fünf",
    "correct": "five",
    "choices": [
      "wide",
      "five",
      "through",
      "most"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sechs",
    "correct": "six",
    "choices": [
      "six",
      "until",
      "who",
      "the"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "acht",
    "correct": "eight",
    "choices": [
      "(one) thousand",
      "to hurt",
      "eight",
      "because"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "neun",
    "correct": "nine",
    "choices": [
      "nine",
      "seventeen",
      "to hike",
      "that"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zehn",
    "correct": "ten",
    "choices": [
      "ninety",
      "of course / naturally",
      "ten",
      "I"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "elf",
    "correct": "eleven",
    "choices": [
      "at the moment",
      "eleven",
      "very",
      "wonderful"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zwölf",
    "correct": "twelve",
    "choices": [
      "twelve",
      "one centimetre",
      "that",
      "heavy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dreizehn",
    "correct": "thirteen",
    "choices": [
      "to be open",
      "loud",
      "thirteen",
      "ten"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vierzehn",
    "correct": "fourteen",
    "choices": [
      "twenty one",
      "fourteen",
      "quarter to/past two (two o’clock)",
      "your"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fünfzehn",
    "correct": "fifteen",
    "choices": [
      "there",
      "ninety",
      "two hundred",
      "fifteen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sechzehn",
    "correct": "sixteen",
    "choices": [
      "there",
      "at",
      "sixteen",
      "to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "siebzehn",
    "correct": "seventeen",
    "choices": [
      "seventeen",
      "at the weekend",
      "one hundred and one",
      "heavy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "achtzehn",
    "correct": "eighteen",
    "choices": [
      "tired",
      "thank you",
      "normal",
      "eighteen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "neunzehn",
    "correct": "nineteen",
    "choices": [
      "of (possessive “s\")",
      "so",
      "nineteen",
      "you"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zwanzig",
    "correct": "twenty",
    "choices": [
      "twenty",
      "first",
      "every",
      "later"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "einundzwanzig",
    "correct": "twenty one",
    "choices": [
      "twenty one",
      "now",
      "again",
      "a single (ticket)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dreißig",
    "correct": "thirty",
    "choices": [
      "funny",
      "from",
      "only",
      "thirty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vierzig",
    "correct": "fourty",
    "choices": [
      "how much",
      "fourty",
      "why",
      "two hundred kilometres"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fünfzig",
    "correct": "fifty",
    "choices": [
      "fifty",
      "little",
      "because",
      "cash"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sechzig",
    "correct": "sixty",
    "choices": [
      "sixty",
      "late",
      "through",
      "what"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "siebzig",
    "correct": "seventy",
    "choices": [
      "where",
      "so",
      "seventy",
      "easy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "achtzig",
    "correct": "eighty",
    "choices": [
      "five",
      "eighty",
      "when",
      "for (an amount of time)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "neunzig",
    "correct": "ninety",
    "choices": [
      "ninety",
      "fifty",
      "two hundred kilometres",
      "free"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(ein)hundert",
    "correct": "(one) hundred",
    "choices": [
      "(one) hundred",
      "two thousand and fourteen",
      "…",
      "thirty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hunderteins",
    "correct": "one hundred and one",
    "choices": [
      "now",
      "one hundred and one",
      "eighty",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zweihundert",
    "correct": "two hundred",
    "choices": [
      "where",
      "until",
      "two hundred",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "(ein)tausend",
    "correct": "(one) thousand",
    "choices": [
      "fifteen",
      "so",
      "(one) thousand",
      "dead"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "erste",
    "correct": "first",
    "choices": [
      "to be on",
      "first",
      "for",
      "expensive"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zweite",
    "correct": "second",
    "choices": [
      "how",
      "until",
      "to be out",
      "second"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dritte",
    "correct": "third",
    "choices": [
      "as",
      "third",
      "and",
      "seventy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vierte",
    "correct": "fourth",
    "choices": [
      "next",
      "to (somewhere)",
      "fourth",
      "him"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "null Uhr drei",
    "correct": "time: 00:03",
    "choices": [
      "above",
      "time: 00:03",
      "left",
      "(one) thousand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sieben Uhr fünfzehn",
    "correct": "time: 07:15",
    "choices": [
      "how much",
      "one gram",
      "time: 07:15",
      "time: 24:00"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "dreizehn Uhr siebzehn",
    "correct": "time: 13:17",
    "choices": [
      "time: 13:17",
      "fourty",
      "how",
      "for (an amount of time)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vierundzwanzig Uhr",
    "correct": "time: 24:00",
    "choices": [
      "sixteen",
      "time: 24:00",
      "so",
      "here"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein Uhr",
    "correct": "one o'clock",
    "choices": [
      "one o'clock",
      "here",
      "brown",
      "second"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "fünf Minuten vor/nach eins (ein Uhr)",
    "correct": "five to/past one (one o’clock)",
    "choices": [
      "in",
      "favourite",
      "five to/past one (one o’clock)",
      "to take (duration)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Viertel vor/nach zwei (zwei Uhr)",
    "correct": "quarter to/past two (two o’clock)",
    "choices": [
      "quarter to/past two (two o’clock)",
      "short",
      "for",
      "until"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "halb drei",
    "correct": "half past two",
    "choices": [
      "next",
      "yellow",
      "half past two",
      "where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein halb; halb",
    "correct": "one half; half",
    "choices": [
      "seventeen",
      "little / not very much",
      "both",
      "one half; half"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein Viertel; Viertel",
    "correct": "one quarter; quarter",
    "choices": [
      "six",
      "one o'clock",
      "one quarter; quarter",
      "long"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "neunzehnhundertneunundneunzig",
    "correct": "nineteen ninety nine",
    "choices": [
      "nineteen ninety nine",
      "to be on",
      "one litre",
      "yourself"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zweitausendvierzehn",
    "correct": "two thousand and fourteen",
    "choices": [
      "fourth",
      "two thousand and fourteen",
      "free",
      "only"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "am Wochenende",
    "correct": "at the weekend",
    "choices": [
      "at the weekend",
      "to be closed",
      "him",
      "here / where we are"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein Meter",
    "correct": "one metre",
    "choices": [
      "fourteen",
      "one metre",
      "little",
      "brown"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein Zentimeter",
    "correct": "one centimetre",
    "choices": [
      "thirty",
      "nineteen",
      "one centimetre",
      "that"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein Meter fünfzehn",
    "correct": "one metre fifteen",
    "choices": [
      "one metre fifteen",
      "simple",
      "to take (duration)",
      "without"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zweihundert Kilometer",
    "correct": "two hundred kilometres",
    "choices": [
      "where",
      "two hundred kilometres",
      "yes",
      "heavy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein Quadratmeter",
    "correct": "one square metre",
    "choices": [
      "she",
      "hello",
      "so",
      "one square metre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein Grad unter Null/minus ein Grad",
    "correct": "one degree below zero/minus one degree",
    "choices": [
      "hello",
      "third",
      "eighteen",
      "one degree below zero/minus one degree"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "vier Grad über Null/plus vier Grad",
    "correct": "four degrees above zero/plus four degrees",
    "choices": [
      "hello",
      "time: 24:00",
      "four degrees above zero/plus four degrees",
      "same"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein Prozent",
    "correct": "one percent",
    "choices": [
      "no",
      "to where",
      "five to/past one (one o’clock)",
      "one percent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein Liter",
    "correct": "one litre",
    "choices": [
      "where",
      "married",
      "why",
      "one litre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein Gramm",
    "correct": "one gram",
    "choices": [
      "quarter to/past two (two o’clock)",
      "now",
      "one gram",
      "this"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein Pfund",
    "correct": "one pound",
    "choices": [
      "one pound",
      "to be gone",
      "every",
      "to where"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ein Kilo(gramm)",
    "correct": "one kilo(gram)",
    "choices": [
      "one kilo(gram)",
      "for example",
      "later",
      "she"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "grau",
    "correct": "grey",
    "choices": [
      "like this",
      "yellow",
      "grey",
      "international"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "gelb",
    "correct": "yellow",
    "choices": [
      "yellow",
      "one hundred and one",
      "eighteen",
      "thirty"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "braun",
    "correct": "brown",
    "choices": [
      "at",
      "from there",
      "well known",
      "brown"
    ]
  }
];
